泰比来劲 泰比来劲 泰比来劲
Juice by Tappy! Juice by Tappy! Juice by Tappy!
噢 泰比真热情有劲
Ohhh,Tappy's got juice! Tappy's got juice!
噢 泰比
Whoa! Tappy!
来劲 来劲 来劲
Juice! Juice! Juice!
你真来劲 你真来劲
Juice by you! Juice by you!
热情有劲 谢谢 谢谢 谢谢
Juice! Juice by you! Thank you, thank you, thank you.
-赢家出来了 -我们有了个赢家
-We got a winner. -We got a winner.
-我说 我们有了个赢家 -我们有了个赢家
-I said, we got a winner. -We got a winner!
我们有了个赢家
We got a winner!
她是一位来自华盛顿的航机服务员
She's a flight attendant from Washington, D.C.
欢迎玛丽·凯林顿
Please welcome Mary Kellington.
玛丽热情有劲 玛丽热情有劲 哦…
Juice by Mary! Juice by Mary! Whoa...
哈瑞 不要再动电视了
Harold, please, not again the TV.
妈 别这样 妈 你为什么非要这样小题大作呢?
Ma, Come on, Ma, Why do you have to make a big deal outta this?
你知道 你几小时内就会把电视赎回来的
You know you'll get the set back in a couple of hours.
为什么要让我有罪恶感呢 妈?
Why you gotta make me feel so guilty, Ma?
老天爷 你想怎么样?
Jesus! What are you doing?
你想让我弄坏电视? 或者天线?
Trying to get me to break my own mother's set? Or radiator?
甚至拆烂整间屋?
And maybe blow up the house?
我是你的儿子 你的血肉 你非要这么对待我吗?
Your own flesh and blood. Is that what you're trying to do? Your son?
为什么老是跟我玩游戏呢? 莫名其妙
Why you play games with my head, for Christ's sake?
哈瑞 你误会了
Harold, I wouldn't do that.
那链子不是针对你的 是防小偷用的
The chain isn't for you. It's for the robbers.
那你怎么不出来?
Then why won't you come out?
知道我的意思吗? 知道你让我有多不开心吗 妈?
See what I mean? See how you always upset me,Ma?
真是的
Christ's sake.
妈?
Ma?
妈!
Ma!
出来好吗 妈?
Come out. Please,Ma?
唉 随你吧!
Ah, screw it!
这不会再发生了
This isn't happening.
如果还是会发生的话 那也不要紧
And if it should be happening, it would be all right.
所以别担心 哈瑞 一切都会没事的
So don't worry, Seymour. It'll all work out.
你已经看过了 到最后 还是会没事的
You'll see already. In the end, it's all nice.
妈的 老兄 这玩意看着都要散架子了
Shit, man. That motherfucker's starting to look a little seedy.
你怎么突然挑惕起来了?
You particular all of a sudden?
我无所谓 只要能得到我们的面包
I don't care, just as long as we get our bread.
帮我一把 泰
Just give me a hand, Tyrone.
看那儿
Look at that.
-你好 -嗨
-Hello. -Hi.
操 连桌子也推来啦
Fuck, the table too!
你要我怎么样? 难道要我背着过来啊?
What do you want? You want me to schlep it on my back?
-不是有他嘛 -我可不是搬运工
-You got a friend. -I ain't my leper's schlepper.
有你这样的儿子 你妈真是不幸
Such a son. Your mother needs you like a moose needs a hat rack.
操 老兄
Shit, man.
这是高档货呀 宝贝
This is some boss scag, baby.
-我的意思是 超赞的 -哦 老兄 真的很特别
-I mean, dynamite. -Oh, man, it's something else.
你知道我们该怎么做吗?
You know what we need to do?
我们应该从布雷迪那买一批货 然后拆开来卖
We need to get us a piece of this Brody shit, cut it up and off it!
我们很容易就可以赚到钱
We could double our money...easy.
一些自己用 一些卖给别人
Buy some pieces and we got some whole other shit.
这样做才对
That'd be righteous.
我打赌我们会很快 直接跟药头拿整磅纯货
I'll bet in no time we'd get a pound of pure straight from Sal the Geep.
噢!
Oooh!
我就是这个意思 毫无疑问
That's what I'm talking about, baby no hassles.
-还好吧? -要什么 老兄?
-How's it goin'? -What's up, buddy?
-照常? -嗯 照常
-The usual? -Yeah, sounds good.
还要点别的吗? 喂?
Anything else? Huh?
-还要什么吗? -哦 不了
-Anything else? -Ah, no.
没事 我很好
Nothing. I'm all right.
-下午好 戈德法布太太 -下午好 拉比诺维茨先生
-Good afternoon, Mrs. Goldfarb. -Good afternoon, Mr. Rabinowitz.
尽管我不确定有多好 你呢?
Although I'm not so sure how good it is. And you?
-我能说什么呢? 你想赎回电视? -对 如果可以的话
-What can I say? You want your TV? -Yes, if you don't mind.
戈德法布太太 我能请教你一件事吗?
Mrs. Goldfarb, can I ask you a question?
不要介意我多嘴问一句
You won't take it personal?
我们认识多久了? 谁能数的清?
How many years we know each other? Who's to count?
你为什么不叫警察? 也许他们会跟哈利谈谈
Why not tell the police? Maybe they could talk to Harry.
-看他还敢偷你的电视 -我不能这样做
-He wouldn't be stealing the TV. -I couldn't do that.
哈瑞是我唯一的孩子 他是我的一切
Harry's my only child. He's all I have.
谢谢你 拉比诺维茨先生
Thank you, Mr. Rabinowitz.
加入我们并创造惊奇 加油!
Join us in creating excellence. JUICE!
你的生活会更有激情
You have more passion for living.
兴奋 兴奋吧
Be excited Be, be excited!
兴奋 兴奋起来吧
兴奋 兴奋吧
Be excited Be, be excited!
兴奋 兴奋起来吧
他们来劲了吗?
They got the juice?
-是的 他们真来劲 -振奋吧
-Yeah, they got the juice. -Juice it up.
你好? 是谁呀?
Hello? Who is it?
妈的 现在呢?
Aw, shit. Now what?
你好?
Hello?
-戈德法布太太吗? -是我 请说
-Mrs. Sara Goldfarb? -Me. Speaking.
我是梅林娱乐集团的莱尔·罗素
This is Lyle Russell from Maylin and Block.
-我没有兴趣 -等一下 我不是要推销东西
-I'm not interested. -Wait. I'm not selling anything.
我只是要给你一个上电视的机会
I just want to offer you a chance to be on television.
上电视?
Television?
是的 戈德法布太太 恭喜你!
That's right, Mrs. Goldfarb. Congratulations!
-不过我没有任何… -我不是为钱
-Look, I don't have any... -I don't want money.
我打电话来告诉你 你赢了
I'm calling to tell you you've already won.
我们为电视节目寻找参赛者
Maylin and Block discovers contestants for TV shows.
而你 被选中了…
You've been chosen from a long list…
也就是说 你赢了
meaning, you've already won.
-噢… -是的 戈德法布太太
-Ohh... -Yes, Mrs. Goldfarb.
我从没想过会上电视 我只是…
I never thought I'd be on television. I'm just...
没错 你会上电视的
That's right. You, on television.
我们会把需要的资料寄给你
We'll send you the necessary information.
再见 恭喜 请保重
Goodbye, congratulations and take care.
我不懂 你为什么对你父母这么反感呢?
But I don't get it. Why are you so hard on your folks?
我是说 他们什么都给你
I mean, they give you everything.
他们供你吃 供你住 还给你找了个心理医生
They hook you up with an apartment, a croaker shrink.
那很好 你知道 是不错 不过…
Which is fine, you know. It's great. It's just...
你知道么? 我想从他们那里得到的并不是钱
Money is never what I really wanted from them, you know?
除了钱他们什么也给不了我
That's pretty much all they have to give.
那为什么不离开他们?
Why don't you get away from 'em?
-我要怎么做呢? -我不知道
-How am I gonna do that? -I don't know.
你的时装设计呢?
What about your clothes?
你有这方面的天赋 可以开个时装店
Your sketches are great. Open up a store.
-我不能 -为什么?
-I can't. -Why not?
那样的话怎么有时间跟你在一起呢?
When will I have time to hang with you?
-哇哦! 要开派对吗? -如果我告诉你 你一定会吓一大跳的
-Well So where's the party? -When I tell you,you're gonna die.
这里紧了点
This is a tough one.
我有本不错的减肥书
I got a great diet book.
嘿
Hey.
他们来了
They're coming.
振奋 振奋吧
Be excited Be, be excited!
我想我应该晒点太阳
I thought I'd catch a little sun today.
是吗? 我想上电视时会有打光
Really? Well, in a box you'll catch it.
只管放松 想想你新染的红发有多靓丽
Just relax and think how gorgeous you'll look with your new red hair.
今天染发 明天晒太阳
Today the hair, tomorrow the sun.
有谁想浪费时间吗?
Anybody wanna waste some time?
天使说现在就是最佳时机
Angel says do it now.
明天我会给布罗迪打电话 布罗迪?
I'll call Brody. Brody?
他是药头 有超赞的货 正点
He gets unbelievable shit. Righteous.
听着 我们有个主意 说来听听?
Look, we got this idea. What is it?
我们进货 拆开卖 赚个双倍
Get a piece of stuff, cut it up and double our money.
再搞整磅的纯货 然后退休
Then get a pound of pure and retire.
你知道那意味着什么吗
You know what that means.
我们不用再辛苦了 我们会过上好日子
We get off hard knocks and on easy street.
到底要做什么呢?
What's the catch?
那是红的 我是说 那是红的
That's a red. I mean, that's a red.
不是纯红 但那是红的 是红的
It's not a red red, but that's a red. It's a red.
-红的? -对 是红的
-Red? -Yeah. It's a red.
-你告诉我这是红的? -是的
-You're telling me that's red? -Yeah.
那橙色是什么?
Then what's orange?
如果这是红的 我想知道... 橙色是什么?
If this is a red, I want to know... what's orange?
呃 它也可以…
Well,it could be…
算是有点偏橙色
That it's a little orange too.
你知道吗?
You know something?
我总是在想 你是我见过的最美的女孩
I always thought you were the most beautiful girl I ever seen.
真的吗?
Really?
从我第一眼见到你 我就知道
Ever since I first saw you.
你真好 哈瑞
That's nice, Harry.
我很开心
That makes me feel really good.
从前也有人对我这样说过
Other people have told me that before,
不过那都没有意义
And it was meaningless.
为什么? 因为你觉得 他们只是想泡你?
Why? Because you thought they were pulling your leg?
不 不是那样 我的意思是…
No,no,not like that. I mean...
我也说不清 或者说我跟本不在乎他们怎么想
I don't know. I don't know or even care if they were.
只是从他们口中说出来...
Just from them it was...
就是毫无意义 你懂吗?
Just meaningless, you know?
但是当你说时 我听到了
When you say it, I hear it.
我真的听到了
I really hear it.
宝贝 你能给我带来好运
Somebody like you could really make things all right for me.
你这样想?
You think?
这是什么?
What is it?
记得我和你说 开店的事么?
Remember when I told you about the store?
恩
Yeah.
我思考了很久 然后...
I've been thinking about it and...
我找了一些资料...
I put together some numbers and...
我觉得这事可行
And it's not impossible!
我是说 你知道吗 你可以做的
I mean,you know,you could do it.
你应该做的
You should do it!
我们可以一起来做
I mean, we could do it together.
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
够了
Stop already.
穿礼服会比吃面包更快乐的
You'll feel better in the red dress than in the cheese Danish.
三件事 三件事改变了我的生活
Three things changed my life. Three.
第一 不吃红肉
Number one. No red meat!
想想看 为何有人偏喜欢红肉?
Think about it. What do they stick in red meat?
我吃红肉到了整块...生吃的地步
I ate red meat to the point where I would eat it... right off,raw.
我喜欢吃肉 但我彻底改变了
I loved my meat. I turned it around.
你要坚定 你要有激情
You need to be committed. You need to be passionate.
三十天不吃红肉 不吃红肉
No red meat for 30 days. No red meat!
三件事 只做这三件事就改变了我的生活
Three things is all I did to change my life. Three things.
艾达告诉我们了 真是太好了
Ada told us. It's gorgeous.
我们明天要把头发颜色再弄深点
We're gonna make it darker tomrrow
-为什么? -好搭配我的红色礼服
-Why? -To go with my red dress.
-可你看起来就像麦当娜 -我不是麦当娜
-But it's looking like Madonna. -It's not Madona
-我也不是 不过很快... -我正在节食
-And neither is this. But soon... -I'm going on a diet.
-怎么节食? -只吃鸡蛋和柚子
-What diet? -Eggs and grapefruit.
-我试过这套 没什么用 -感觉没那么糟
-I was on that. Lots of luck. -It's not so bad.
-你进行节食多久了? -整天
-How long you been on it? -All day.
整天! 现在才下午一点
All day! It's one o'clock!
-我想变瘦 -她确实想变瘦
-No,I'm thinking thins. -She's thinking thins.
我家路易丝就那样瘦了50磅
My Louise,she lost 50 pounds just like that.
- 怎样? - 一下子就瘦了
-Like what? -Poof!
难道你把她放在发汗箱里了?
Did you put her in a sweatbox?
她吃了医生给开的药就瘦了 你不会想吃的
She went to a doctor and he gave her pills. You don't want to eat.
你的意思是 可以坐在这不去想面包上的熏肉吗?
So? You mean,I'm sitting here not thinking about pastrami on rye?
你不该在别人节食的时候说这样的话
Don't talk like that when someone's on a diet.
没关系 我会再偷吃片柚子的
Big deal. I'll sneak another wedge of grapefruit.
-我想瘦 -嘿 莎拉 邮差来了
-I'm thinking thins. -Ooh,Sara,the mailman.
莎拉·戈德法布 有我的信么? 我在等我的信
Sara Goldfarb?You have something for Sara Goldfarb?I'm expecting something.
戈德法布 戈德法布 莎拉·戈德法布
Goldfarb,Goldfarb. Sara Goldfarb.
-是这封吗? -就是这封
-Is that it? -That's it!
-快点 -等一下 我要先拿东西
-Come on. -I gotta get my stuff.
-好的 -我告诉你怎么写
-All right. -I can tell you.
名字 填上你的名字
Your name. Put your name.
S-A-R-A G-O-l-D...
F-A-R-B!
"非同凡响"?(指海洛因)
Dynamite?
对 是"非同凡响"
It's Dynamite.
啊哈 "非同凡响"!
A- ha Dynamite!
没问题 我们马上过去
All right,we're on our way.
-布罗迪的人说有高档货了 -好吧 老兄
-Brody's man says it's fine shit. -All right,man.
-就是这样 -嘿 泰
-Here we go. -Hey,Ty?
-兄弟 我们不能出差错 -宝贝 自然点
-Let's do this right,man. -Come on,baby. Naturally.
-快点 快点 我们快点 -不知道什么时候才轮到你
-Hurry,hurry. Let's hurry. -I wonder when you'll hear.
-嗨 -我想跟你一起去
-Hi -I wanna come with you!
也许她们会送你到绿茵小舍 明星都在那里
Maybe they'll send you to Tavern On The Green,you know,that's where they send all the stars.
恩 我要在那儿吃鸡蛋和柚子
Yeah,eggs and grapefruit at Tavern On The Green.
-我希望他们有提供 -趁邮差还没来 快点
-I hope they have that. -Hurry before the mailman comes.
-好了 -寄出去吧
-Here we are. -Mail it!
噢 莎拉
Oh,Sara!
-拿到了 哥们 -啊?
-There it is,Jim. -Huh?
-在这里 宝贝 -噢 靠
-There it is,baby. -Oh,shit!
-我们试试吧? -等等 泰
-Shall we try it? -Wait,Ty.
听着 这是我们发财的机会
Look,this is our chance to make it big.
好好做 我们就可以弄到整磅的纯货
We play it right,we can get a pound of pure.
可是如果我们浪费了...
But if we get wasted...
- 一切就搞砸了 - 我知道
-We'll fuck it up. -Right on.
听我说 哥们 你误会了
Hey,look,I ain't trying to jive you,Jim.
我也不想一辈子就在街上混
I don't wanna be runnin' the streets my whole life,
挨冻受饿
my nose runnin' down to my chin.
我的意思是先尝一点 这样才能知道该怎么分
All I'm sayin' is take a little taste so we know how much to cut.
纯是为生意
It's business.
恩 也有道理
Yeah,fair enough.
靠…
Shit...
谢谢大家 我只做了三件事
Thank you. Three things is all I did.
只花了三十天
30 days is all it takes.
第二 不吃精制糖
Number two. No refined sugar!
现在 糖无所不在
Now,sugar's everywhere.
你知道吗? 商家甚至在瓶装水里也放糖
You know they even put sugar in bottled water?
我曾得了嗜糖症 那曾是我的药
I was sick with sugar. That was my medicine.
它浸蚀我的大脑 让我觉得自己是个失败者
It nurtured my spiralling brain that felt I was a loser.
振作起来!
Juice by you!
第二条守则 不吃精制糖
Rule two is no refined sugar.
汽水? 连想都不要想了
Sodas? Don't even think about sodas any more.
不要再吃糖果 一点也不要吃 远离它
No sucking candies. None of that. Just stay away from it.
30天不吃精制糖
No refined sugar. For 30 days.
我要吃得健康
I'm gonna eat right.
我要打起精神 我要放手一搏
I am gonna pick up my spirits and I am gonna try!
我找到了希望 在希望中找到了方法...
I found hope. And in that hope,I found a way...
闭嘴!
Shut up!
你好?
Hello?
-罗西? -是
-Rosie? -Yeah.
-我是莎拉 -嗯?
-Sara. -Yeah?
我需要你说的那个医生的电话
I need the number of that doctor.
我不明白 你为什么非要去见他
I don't understand why you gotta see him.
真他妈的 你不要再理他了
Cut the son of a bitch loose,for Christ's sake.
如果不去 他会告诉我父母我没有接受心理治疗
Because he'll tell my parents that I've stopped therapy.
他们已经开始考虑和我断绝关系了
They're already thinking of cutting me off.
哈瑞 我又不会和他上床
Harry,I'm not gonna sleep with him.
演奏会结束我就回来了
I'm gonna come home after the concert.
你在吃醋!
You're jealous!
哈瑞... 你在吃醋?
Harry... jealous?
-抱住我 -不要
-Put your arms around me. -No.
你还真不听话 抱住我
You are so stubborn. Put your arms around me.
别闹了!
Stop that!
-我要把你的眼球吸出来 -嗯
-I'll suck your eyeballs out. -Mm-hm.
嗯...
Well...
我很失望你不自在
I'm disappointed that you're indisposed.
阿妮塔是外出了还是怎么了?
Is Anita out of town or something?
为什么这么问?
Why do you ask?
我只是想知道她是否 "不自在"
I was just wondering if she was "indisposed".
没有
No.
她很好 谢谢 事实上 她在佛罗里达
She's fine,thank you. Actually,she's in Florida.
-我能问你个私人问题吗 阿诺德? -当然
-Can I ask you something personal,Arnold? -Of course.
什么事? 说吧
Anything. What?
-你这里沾了点东西 -还有么?
-You just have something here. -Gone?
往下一点 再往下一点
A little bit,a little bit lower.
没事了 别担心 好多了
It's OK. Don't worry. It's much better.
阿诺德!
Arnold!
你感觉如何 戈德法布太太?
How are you,Mrs Goldfarb?
我如何? 身躯庞大 所以我才来这
How am I? Enormous. That's why I'm here.
-我看过情况更糟的 -哦... 谢谢
-I've seen much worse. -Oh... thank you.
-你的听力和视力怎么样? -都很好
-How's your hearing and vision? -I have both.
医生等一下就来
The doctor will be with you shortly.
-你有点过重 -只是有点?
-You're a little overweight. -A little?
如果可以 我愿意捐50磅出来
I have 50 pounds I'm willing to donate.
我们可以处理 没问题
We can take care of that. No problem.
我们要发了 宝贝
We're on our way,baby.
我们要发了
We are on our way!
天啊 那里真棒 我的意思是每个人都很 渴
God,it was great out there. I mean,everybody is thirsty.
过来
Come to me.
哈瑞 我好高兴
Harry,I am so glad.
自然的
Naturally.
紫色的早上吃
Purple in the morning.
蓝色的下午吃
Blue in the afternoon.
晚上吃橘黄色的
Orange in the evening.
这就是我的三餐 自以为是的家伙
There's my three meals,Mr Smarty-pants.
绿色的夜里吃 就像那样
And green at night. Just like that.
一 二 三 四
One,two,three,four.
回床上来 亲爱的
Come back to bed,baby.
等一下 爱丽丝 时间有的是
Come on,Alice. Got plenty of time for that.
我正在装配新的活门镜子
Right now I'm grooving with these new mirrors I got.
呼!
Oooh!
妈 我跟你说 我以后一定会出人头地
I told ya,Mom,one day I'd make it.
你不必出人头地 宝贝
You don't have to make anything,my sweet.
你只要爱妈妈就好了 嗯?
You just have to love your mama,huh?
你在干什么 亲爱的?
What are you doin',baby?
嗯?
Huh?
-你在干什么 亲爱的? -没干什么
-What are you doin',baby? - Nothin'.
我在想你
Just thinkin' about you.
在想我跟你接下来要做的下流事
About the nasty things I'm about to do to ya.
婊子 给我过来!
Bitch,get over here!
泰 你吓到我了
Ty,you scare me to death.
不 我不会吓你 我不想吓任何人
No,I wouldn't scare you. I don't wanna scare nobody.
我只想生活平静而快乐 这就够了
All I want out of life is a bit of peace and happiness. That's all.
现在...
Right now...
你是我见过最漂亮的狐狸精
you're the finest fox I ever laid my eyes on.
-我想要做件事 -嗯?
-That's what I'll do. -Hmm?
我一直想给我妈买点东西
For my mother. I've been thinking about getting something for her.
比如... 一件礼物什么的
Like... a present or something.
我一直不知道该给她买什么
But I didn't know what I was gonna get,until now.
-然后? -最后我问我自己
-And? -I finally asked myself,right,
她着迷什么?
what's her fix?
电视 对吧?
Television,right?
她是一个不折不扣的电视迷
I mean,if ever there's a TV junkie,it's the old lady.
之前那台总是让我搬来搬去 已经磨损的很严重了
I figure I owe her a new set,anyway with all the wear and tear it got
我欠她一台新电视
being schlepped back and forth to old all the time.
你很爱她 是吧?
You really love her,don't you?
我想是吧 你知道吗?
I guess so. You know?
我一直希望她快乐
Most of the time I just want her to be happy.
我们现在就去买一台
Let's go get it now.
我们要先离开这里
Let's push off first.
现在还早 哈瑞 我们晚上再出发吧
It's early,Harry. We shouldn't get going till tonight.
兴奋 兴奋吧
Be excited. Be,be excited.
兴奋吧
Be excited.
要坚定 而且有激情
Be committed and be passionate.
我是个活生生的例子 瘦了65磅 我感觉棒极了!
I am a living testament. 65 pounds thinner. I feel great!
第三 噢 第三件
Number three. Ohhh,number three!
这让很多人疯狂
This drives most people crazy.
目前为止都很容易
This is easy so far.
-瘦了 -她跟以前不一样了
-That is thin. -She's not the same person.
我已经瘦了很多 就快要穿上那件红礼服了
I can almost zip the red dress. I've almost got the zipper up.
-莎拉 邮差来了 -噢!
-Sara. The mailman -Oh!
戈德法布 有你的信我会第一时间给你的
Goldfarb. When I see it I'll wave it all over the place.
-你确定吗? -是的 我确定
-Are you sure? You... -Yeah,I'm sure.
-他说的什么? -别担心 莎拉 一定会来的
-What did he say? -Don't worry,Sara,it'll come.
是啊 别担心 会来的
Yeah,don't worry. It'll come.
是哈瑞!
It's Harry!
哈瑞 噢!
Harry,oh!
嘿 妈 轻一点 你要把我挤扁了
Hey,Ma,easy. You'll crush me,for Christ sakes.
-进屋吧 -大家好
-Come inside. -Hello.
嗨 哈瑞! 你好! 有客人来喽
Hi,Harry! Hello! We'll have a little visit.
过得怎么样 哈瑞? 你看起来不错
So,how are you,Harry? You look so good.
-想吃点什么吗? -不了 妈
-You want something to eat? -No, Ma.
点心 或者蛋糕? 如果你想吃我可以再出去弄些
A little nosh,maybe a piece of cake? I could go out and get something,if you want.
家里没什么东西了 不过艾达阿姨那儿有
I don't have anything in the house,but Ada would have something.
来个小蛋糕? 要吃点什么?
A cup of cake,baby? You want something to eat?
不 妈 什么都不要 坐下好吗
No,no,Ma,nothing. Please,sit.
你让我头昏眼花的
You make me dizzy,for Christ's sake.
你发现我有啥不同吗? 注意到我变瘦了吗?
You notice anything about me,huh? You notice I'm slimmer?
好像是瘦了
Yeah,I guess you are.
25磅 我瘦了25磅 你相信吗?
25 pounds,I lost. 25 pounds! Can you believe it?
-而且这只是个开始而已 -那很好 妈 很好
-And that's only the beginning.-That's great,Ma. It's really great!
我真的很为你高兴 但是你坐下来好吗? 拜托
I'm really happy for you. But,but will you sit? Please.
很抱歉我没回家好一阵子了 但我一直很忙 真的很忙
I'm sorry I haven't been around in a while,Ma,but I've been busy,real busy.
是吗? 你有好工作了? 做得好吗?
Oh,yeah? You got a good job? You're doing really well?
-恩 很好 真的很好 -什么工作呢?
-Yeah,reay good,real good. -What kind of business?
嗯 有点像经销商 为大进口商做销售
Well,I'm sort of a distributor like,for a big importer.
-哇! 我真为你高兴 -妈... 轻点 这样我会死的
-Ohh! I'm so happy for you.-Ma...Easy.You're killin' me.
天啊 你一直在练举重吗?
Jesus,what,you've been lifting weights?
-我就知道你行的 -你是对的 妈
-I always knew you could do that. -You were right,Ma.
准备找个好女孩 然后生个小孩?
Now,maybe you'll meet a nice girl and have a baby?
我已经认识一个了
Well,I already met one.
-啊! -妈 别这么夸张
-Ahh! -Ma,Ma,Ma,don't,don't go ape shit,all right?
-她是谁? 谁家的女孩? 做什么的? -你认识的
-Who is she? Who's her parents? What do they do? -You know her,Ma.
-玛丽安 玛丽安·希尔瓦 记得吗? -噢 希尔瓦!
-Marion. Marion Silver. Remember? -Oh,Silver!
当然 曼哈顿海滩
Of course. Manhattan Beach.
他在海边有幢别墅 做服装生意
He's got a house on the esplanade. Garment business.
恩 做女性内衣生意的大亨
He's a real big one in women's undies.
妈 你别走来走去了 我有事要说
Before you go bouncing all over again and make me forget,Ma. Just...
我想告诉你 我有件礼物要给你
What I wanna tell you is that I got you a present.
我不需要礼物 我只想要个孙子
I don't need a present. Just have a baby.
你能让我说完么 别打岔 妈!
Will you let me tell you what I got ya? Will ya, Ma?
天啊 你今天真的有点反常 你知道吗?
Christ,you are really something else today,you know that?
听我说 我知道...
Look,I know...
嗯…
Well...
很抱歉我一直不学好 我很想补偿你
I'm sorry for being such a bastard. I wanna make it up.
我知道 我不能改变已经发生过的事
I mean,I know I can't change anything that's happened,
但是我希望你知道...
But I want you to know that...
我很爱你 而且 我很抱歉
That I love you,and that I'm sorry.
我希望你快乐 所以我给你买了台新电视
And I want you to be happy. So I got you a brand-new TV set.
过几天就会送来了 还是个名牌呢
It's gonna be delivered in a couple of days. It's from Macy's!
噢 哈瑞!
Oh,Harry!
你父亲会很开心的
Your father'd be so happy...
如果他看到你为我做的这些事
if he could see what you're doing for your mother.
看到了吗 老头子?
See that,Seymour?
你儿子现在懂事了
You see how good your son is?
他知道他妈一个人独居很孤单
He knows what it's like for his mother living all alone.
没人来看她
No one to visit her.
嘿 妈
Hey,Ma.
-你在磨牙吗? -什么?
-You on uppers? -What?
你在磨牙 你在吃减肥药 是吗?
You're on uppers. You're on diet pills,ain't you?
我跟你说了 我去看了专科医生
I told you. I'm going to a specialist.
正如我想 你让体重急速下降 是不是?
That's what I thought. You make your croaker on speed,ain't you?
哈瑞 你还好吧 我是去看医生
Harry,are you all right. I'm goin' to a doctor.
他给了你什么 他给你药片了吗?
What does he give you,Ma? Does he give you pills?
当然给了我药片 他是医生
Of course.He gives me pills.He's a doctor.
-什么样的药片? -有紫的 蓝的 还有橘黄色的...
-What kind of pills? -A purple one,a blue one,an orange one...
我的意思是 里面含什么?
I mean,like what's in 'em?
哈瑞 我是戈德法布 又不是爱因斯坦 我怎么知道里面有什么
Oh,Harry. I'm Sara Goldfarb,not Albert Einstein. How should I know what 's in it?
那些玩意是不是让你感觉很好 而且充满活力?
Does this stuff make you feel good,soft and give you lots of pep?
呃... 是吧 有一点
Well...Yeah,a little.
一点? 我在这儿就听得到你磨牙的声音
A little? Ma,I can hear ya grinding your teeth from here.
-晚上就不会了 -晚上?
-That goes away at night. -At night?
对啊 睡前吃绿色药片 30分钟后一下子就睡着了
Yeah,when I take the green one. 30 minutes I'm asleep. Poof,just like that.
妈 你必须戒掉那些药片
Ma,Ma,you gotta cut that stuff loose.
我告诉你 那玩意是有害的
I'm tellin' you,it's no good.
你怎么知道那不是好东西? 我都瘦了25磅啊
What do you mean it's no good? 25 pounds I've lost.
那有什么大不了的? 难道你想变成一个瘾君子吗?
Big deal. So what? You wanna be a dope fiend,for Christ's sake
瘾君子? 你看到我口吐白沫了吗? 人家是个好医生
What a dope fiend? Am I foaming at the mouth? There's something,he's a nice doctor.
我告诉你 那家伙一点都不好
I am telling you, that croaker is no good.
你怎么会知道这么多? 你怎么会比医生更懂药呢?
How come you know so much? How come you know more about medicine than a doctor?
相信我 妈 我真的知道 好吗?
Believe me,Ma,I know. All right?
你会上瘾的
You'll get strung out for Christ's sake.
噢 别这样 我快要穿上那件红礼服了
Ah,come on I almost fit in my red dress.
就是参加你高中毕业典礼穿的那件
The one I wore to your high school graduation.
你爸爸非常喜欢那件
The one your father liked so much.
噢 我现在仍然记得他看我的眼神
Oh,I remember how he looked at me in that red dress.
妈 为啥非要穿上那件红礼服呢?
Ma what's the big deal about the red dress?
我要穿它上...
I'm going to wear it at...
你还不知道!
You don't know!
我要上电视了 我接到了电话和申请书...
I'm gonna be on television. I got a call and an application...
得啦 妈 谁在跟你开玩笑?
Come on,Ma,who's pulling your leg?
不 不 不 我跟你说
No,no,no.I'm tellin' ya.
我要上电视当个参赛者了
I'm gonna be a contestant on television.
他们还没有告诉我什么时候上
I don't know when yet. They haven't told me when yet,
不过当你看到你妈穿着红礼服上电视时 你一定会很骄傲的
but you'll see how proud you're when you see your mother in her red dress on television and golden shoes.
上电视有什么大不了的? 那些药片在你上电视之前就会要了你的命
What's the big deal about being on television? Those pills will take you and kill you before you get on for Christ's sake
没什么大不了的?
"Big deal?"
坐计程车的时候
You drove up in a cab.
你知道谁坐最好的位子吗?
Did you see who had the best seat?
我现在不是普通人了 哈瑞
I'm somebody now,Harry.
大家都喜欢我
Everybody likes me.
很快...
Soon...
成千上万的人会看到我 而且都会喜欢我
millions of people will see me and they'll all like me.
我会跟他们说起你...
I'll tell them about you...
还有你爸爸
your father.
告诉他们你爸爸对我们有多好
How good he was to us.
记得吗?
Remember?
这就是为什么我早上起床
It's a reason to get up in the morning.
这就是为什么我要减肥
It's a reason to lose weight,to fit in the red dress.
这让我微笑
It's a reason to smile.
这让明天更美好
It makes tomorrow all right.
我得到了什么 哈瑞?
What have I got,Harry?
嗯?
Hmm?
为什么我还要整理床铺和洗碗?
Why should I even make the bed or wash the dishes?
这些我都做 但是为什么?
I do them,but why should I?
我很孤单
I'm alone.
你爸爸走了 你也离开了我
Your father's gone,you're gone.
我没有人可以...
I got no one to...
照顾
care for.
我得到了什么 哈瑞?
What have I got,Harry?
我很寂寞
I'm lonely.
而且我老了
I'm old.
你还有朋友啊 妈
You got friends,Ma.
不 那不一样的
Hmm... It's not the same.
她们不需要我
They don't need me.
我喜欢现在这样的感觉
I like the way I feel.
我喜欢想着红礼服...
I like thinking about the red dress...
想着上电视 还有你和你爸爸
and the television and you and your father.
现在我看到阳光就会微笑
Now when I get the sun,I smile.
我会经常回来看你的 妈
I'll come and visit,Ma.
现在我的生意也上了轨道 我会回来看你的
Now that I'm straight,m-my business is going good,I'll come.
我会带玛丽安回来吃晚饭的
Me and Marion,we'll come for dinner.
很好 带她来吧
Good.You bring her.
我会给你们做好吃的
I'll make you mushroom soup and a roast.
听起来不错 妈 很不错
That sounds great,Ma. That sounds great.
-来之前我会给你打电话的 -好
-I'll give you a call ahead a time,all right? -OK.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
我很高兴你有个不错的女朋友 还有自己的生意 我很高兴
I'm glad you have a nice girl and your own business. I'm glad.
我该走了 妈
I gotta go,Ma.
我在曼哈顿跟人有约
I got an appointment in Manhattan in a little bit,
不过 不过我会回来的
but...but I'll be back.
-好 你...你还有家里钥匙是吗? -恩 我有
-OK,y-you still got your key? -Yeah,I got it,Ma.
再见 儿子
Bye, Son.
布罗迪说你反应很快
Brody says you comin' up quick,kid.
噢 谢啦 老兄
Oh. Thanks,man.
他说你很聪明 很忠诚 而且不是个毒鬼
He says you're smart,you're loyal and you're not a junkie.
布罗迪想提拔你
Brody wants to promote you.
想给你个好差事 有兴趣吗?
He wants to give you more responsibility. You interested?
有 当然
Yeah,yeah!
当然有兴趣
Shit,yeah,man.
布罗迪说 你敢背判他 就让我杀了你
Brody says,you fuck him,I kill you.
-绝对不会 -最好不会
-I got that. -Remember that.
靠 你有个白人司机!
Shit. You got a white driver!
操!
Fuck!
搞什么鬼?
What the fuck?
别动!
Don't move!
我爱你 哈瑞
I love you,Harry.
你让我觉得自己是个真正的人
You make me feel like a person.
是我自己...
Like I'm me...
让我觉得我很美
and I'm beautiful.
你本来就很美
You are beautiful.
你是世界上最美的女人
You're the most beautiful girl in the world.
你是我的梦中情人
You're my dream.
不 我非常确定 我已经查过了
No,Mrs Goldfarb,I'm absolutely certain. I've checked again.
可能你们上次给我的药效较弱
But maybe you gave me a weaker one last time.
不可能的 戈德法布太太 药效都是一样的
That isn't possible,Mrs Goldfarb. Like you see,they're all the same potency.
可是感觉不一样啊
But something isn't the same.
你只是渐渐习惯了 没什么好担心的 好吗?
You're just becoming adjusted to them.It's nothing to worry about,Mrs Goldfarb.OK?
-我们有了优胜者! -优胜者产生了!
-We got a winner! -We got a winner!
-我们有了优胜者! -她很漂亮 富有幽默感
-We got a winner! -She's a beautiful woman,with a winning sense of humour
有着魔法般的笑容
And magical smile.
让我们热烈欢迎 来自布鲁克林的
Straight from Brighton Beach,Brooklyn,let's give a juice welcome...
莎拉·戈德法布女士!
to Mrs Sara Goldfarb!
莎拉热情有劲! 莎拉热情有劲! 噢!
Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Ohh...!
莎拉热情有劲! 莎拉热情有劲! 噢! 莎拉!
Sara juice! Sara juice! Ohh...! Sara!
嘿 泰
Love...Love,Tyrone C.
收拾一下你的东西 有人来保你了
Get your shit together. You made bail.
花了多少钱?
How much?
花了我们大部份的现金 你的价钱涨了
They got most of our cash. You're up for consortin'.
该死的!
Oh,shit,man!
安吉尔说 意大利人跟黑人在争斗
Angel says there's a war between the Italians and Blacks.
他说货会留在佛罗里达 除非布罗迪的势力消失
He says Sal the Geep is keeping all the shit down in Florida until guys like Brody are all knocked off.
狗屎
Shit.
-没有人能拿到货 -除了蒂姆老大
-No one's got a thing. -Except Big Tim.
靠 我们去找他
Shit. Let's go see him.
他不卖的 他只给娘们
He's not sellin'. He's only givin' up for pussy.
什么?
What?
娘们 他就喜欢那一套
Pussy. He hooked on that thing,man
我说我会满足他要的一切 他说我不和他的口味
I told I'd give him all he wants. He said I ain't cute enough for him
-第三件事! -第三件!
-Number three! -Ohh,number three!
这会让很多人发疯
This drives most people crazy.
他们不会喜欢的
They're not gonna like it.
到现在都还算容易 戒除30天 就会...
This is easy so far. Give it up for 30 days,it will...
你还好吧?
You all right?
没事 只是个恶梦
No care. It was just a bad dream.
要喝点水吗?
Want some water?
也许我们现在该打一针
Maybe we should dip in now.
怎么回事 玛丽安 我已经和你说过了
Come on,Marion. I already told you,all right?
我们就剩这些了
It's all we have.
泰早上会带来些的 哈瑞
Tyrone is gonna score in the morning,Harry.
不好意思 我只是...
I don't know,it's...
只是有些烦躁
It's a bitch out there.
会没事的
It'll be OK.
会没事的 哈瑞
It'll be OK,Harry.
是啊...
Yeah...
我想是吧
I guess so.
我爱你 哈瑞
I love you,Harry.
有什么问题吗? 你的体重正常
What's the problem? The weight's fine.
体重正常 但我不
The weight's fine,I'm not.
电冰箱...
The refrigerator...
怎么了?
Something wrong?
每样东西都...
Everything's...
混在了一起
All mixed up.
-很混乱... -没什么好担心的
-Confused... -Nothing to worry about.
填好这张表 下星期再来看下就可以了
Just get this filled. Make an appointment for a week.
怎么了?
Well?
泰没拿到货
Ty ain't found anythin' yet.
那我们怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
哈瑞 你得想点办法
Well,you have to do something,Harry.
因为你 我们早上什么也没有
I mean,it's your fault we don't have something in the morning.
-你在胡说什么? -你昨晚把剩下的都吸完了
-What're you talking about? -You were all hot in the biscuit to get off last night.
-简直胡扯! -如果你没有都吸光 我们现在就有东西了
-That is such bullshit. -You didn't have to,OK? And We could have had something right now.
我该怎么做? 难道要我一个人做在这看着你离开么?
What Was I supposed to do? I'm gonna sit around and watch you push off and not go myself?
不要都往我身上推
Just don't put it all on me,OK?
别担心 老兄 我们会再装满它的
Don't worry,man. We'll fill it up again.
情况会好转的
You know,things'll be better,
到时我们就能再装满它了
then we'll be fillin' the box back up,you know?
想听听新的消息吗?
So,you wanna hear the news?
什么消息?
What news?
有好消息 也有坏消息
You got your good news,you got your bad news.
说吧
Shoot.
好消息是
Good news is,
再过几天 街上会出现高档货
A couple of days,there's gonna be some prime back on the street.
-是吗? -恩
-Really? -Mm-hm.
谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?
-安吉尔 -是嘛?
-Angel. -Yeah?
意大利人发话说 在圣诞节期间放点东西出来
Sal the Geep has sent words to the street,let a couple of keys go for Christmas season,
他是个好基督徒
You know him,being a good Christian and,
不想破坏过节的气氛
not wantin' bad feelin' during this glorious season.
-你不会真信吧? -开始相信...
-You fuck believe it? -Well,I did...
直到我听到坏消息
till I heard the bad news.
什么坏消息?
Yeah?
价钱加倍 还得按重量买
Price is double. You have to cop for weight.
-至少一半的基本量 -多少钱?
-At least half a piece. -How much?
-两个数 -两个数?
-Two. -Two?
-神经病啊! -不然又能怎样?
-That's fuckin' insane. -What you gonna do?
不会有人白送给你的
Man ain't goin' to lay nickel bag on you for damn sure.
我们去哪儿弄那么多钱啊?
Where we gonna get two?
你是说阿诺德?
You mean Arnold?
你父母甚至都不回你电话
Well,your parents won't even return your call.
我有几个月没见过他了
I haven't seen him in months.
-那又如何? 他不是经常给你打电话么? -我不知道
-So what? He's still callin',ain't he? -I don't know.
听着 我是真没有办法了
Look,I don't know what else to do.
这是我们最后的机会了
Ok,this is our last chance to get back on track!
抓住这次机会我们就不用这么无休止的争吵了
We won't have to scuffle and make that freezing scene every day!
我们需要钱
We need the bread.
问题不是弄到钱 哈瑞
Getting the money is not the problem,Harry.
天啊 那问题是什么?
What is the problem? For Christ's sake.
问题是怎么从他那儿弄到钱
I don't know what I'll have to do to get it.
听着...
Look...
宝贝...
Baby...
我们很快就会把生意再做起来
we'll be back in business in no time.
很快我们就会重回轨道
We'll start movin' again.
并积累财富
And we'll start savin'.
一切都会很顺利的 就像从前一样 我保证
It'll be perfect,just like it was. I promise,Marion.
你会看到的
You'll see.
不 我只是 呃... 感觉就像我的感冒永远也好不了了
No,I've just,uh... I've had this flu forever,it seems like.
-你很沮丧吗? -不 不是那样的
-Are you depressed? -No,it's nothing like that.
我只是 呃... 我只是最近很忙
I've been,uh... I've been really busy.
事实上 我一直在设计服装
Actually,I've been designing... non-stop.
不错 你能有事可做真的很好
Wonderful. Glad to hear you've been productive.
老实说吧
To be perfectly frank,
接到你的电话我有惊讶
I was a little surprised to hear from you.
-遇到麻烦了么? -没有 为什么这样问?
-Is there something wrong? -No. Why?
当你打给很久没联系的人时 通常是因为有事
Well,it's usually the case... you gotta call for someone you haven't heard for a while.
一切都很好
Everything's fine.
实际上
Actually
我有事相求
I have a favour to ask.
王八蛋!
You smug fuck!
什么事?
What is it?
我想借点钱
I need to borrow some money.
我能知道这是为了什么吗?
May I ask what for?
-把灯关掉好吗? -为什么要关灯?
-Could you turn the light off? -Why do you want the light off?
没有为什么
I just do.
-难道你以前也这样? -拜托 阿诺德
-You never did before. -Please,Arnold.
-人都在哪里? -我不知道 老兄
-Where is everybody? -I don't know,man.
安吉尔只说在超市碰面
All Angel said was meet at Waldbaum's.
-确定是这家超市吗? -对 我确定
-You sure this is the right Waldbaum's? -Yeah,man. I'm positive,all right?
我们两个互相保护着点
Look,you just watch my back,and I'll watch yours.
-现在该怎么办? -瞧那儿
-What are we supposed to do now? -Hey.
所有人都来了
Everyone and their mother.
卡车就在这停 都后退
The truck's gonna be here. Back up.
往后退
Back up.
回来!
Come back!
去他妈的药头! 我们被耍了! 我们被 耍了
Stupid fuckin' junkie,man! We're fucked! We are fucked.
-这是我们最后的机会了 -狗日的在佛罗里达晒太阳
-That's our last shit for miles,man. -Sitting on their asses in sun
我们却在这里挨冻
while we sit here ass deep in motherfuckin' snow.
嘿 我们也去佛罗里达怎么样?
Hey. What would happen if we went down there to cop?
-你开什么玩笑? -不是玩笑
-Are you serious? -Why not?
你瞎说的什么啊?
What the fuck are you sayin'?
难道随便去找个狗屁旅馆 问人家有没有卖毒品的住进来?
Goin' up to the motherfucker room clerk at some hotel and askin' for a connection?
管它呢 你不是告诉我 毒品在周围的时候你就能闻到么?
Get with it. You tellin' me you can nose our some dope when it's around?
老兄 我们没什么可失去的了 现在正是大好时机
Man,we got nothin' to lose. It's wide open.
如果我们现在就去的话 回来后 价格就是我们说了算
And if we get there right away we can name our own price,
那群毒鬼会自动拿着钱给我们送来的
and sit back and be cool and have those fucking fools scufflin' the streets for us.
是呀 老兄 去年夏天真他妈的开心 是吧?
Yeah,man. Last summer was a motherfuckin' ball,huh,Jim?
感觉那个夏天已经过去1000年了
Just seems like a thousand years ago since last summer,man.
哥们 我们会再像那时一样的
It'll be like that again,man.
安吉尔会告诉我们路线的...
I could get Angel to get us a short...
只要我们保证给他带回些高档货
if we promise him some dynamite scag.
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
你以为我去哪儿了?
Where the hell you think I've been?
-货呢? -我们碰到了一点麻烦
-Where's the score? -Well,we had a little bit of a problem,you see.
我是说 本来一切进展顺利 后来...
I mean,everything was goin' good,and then...
-有些毒鬼... -做什么了?
-some dumb-ass junkie... -Did what?
有些毒鬼做什么了? 你搞砸了是吧?
Some dumb-ass junkie did what? You mean you fucked it up?!
-你在发什么神经? -你向我保证过不会有问题 还记得吗?
-What the fuck is wrong with you? -You promised me that everything was gonna be OK,remember?
为了你 我跟那个混球搞 为了你 我什么都做
I fucked that sleazebag for you. I put myself through fucking hell for you!
-就是没有货嘛 -我才不管 你个狗日的!
-There's nothing out there -I don't give a shit. You fucking loser!
你以为我们私藏了是吧?
You wanna be sure we have some extra stuff?
泰说有个家伙有货
Ty told me about a guy holding some weight.
但是他不卖!
But he ain't sellin' it!
喂?
Yeah?
-给我那家伙的电话 -哪个?
-Ty,give me that guy's number. -What guy?
-喜欢娘们的那个 -要他电话干嘛?
-The guy who likes broads -Tell me... Why?
你他妈的告诉我就是了 哪来这么多废话
Just give me the fucking number for Christ's sake!
好 好 934-8777
All right,all right. 934-8777.
既然你这么烦的话 你自己去和那家伙搞吧!
You worried so goddam much. Here,go fix yourself up with him!
这样你就不用再等了 我也不用在外面挨冻了
You won't have to fucking wait around so much,and I won't have to freeze my ass off the fuckin' streets.
狗日的
Fuck you.
-好了 优胜者出现了 -优胜者!
-All right,we got a winner. -We got a winner!
-优胜者出现了 - 优胜者!
-We got a winner. -We got a winner!
-优胜者出现了 -优胜者!
她很漂亮 富有幽默感 有着魔法般的笑容
She's a beautiful woman,with a winning sense of humour and magical smile.
她将赢得你们的心!
She is really gonna win your heart!
让我们热烈欢迎
Straight from Brighton Beach,Brooklyn.
来自布鲁克林的莎拉·戈德法布太太!
Please give a juicy welcome to our very own Mrs Sara Goldfarb!
莎拉热情有劲! 莎拉热情有劲! 噢! 莎拉!
Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Ohh...! Sara!
噢! 莎拉!
Ohh...! Sara!
能到这里来我很高兴
It's a pleasure to be here.
我们也很高兴 你的衣服真漂亮
It's a pleasure to have you. And that is one smashing dress you have on.
谢谢 如果你不介意 我想跟我先生西蒙打声招呼
Thank you,Tappy. If you don't mind,I would just like to say hello to my husband,Seymour,
还有我那英俊有为的儿子 哈瑞
and my beautiful,successful son,Harold.
我希望你一切顺利
I hope you're in love.
带玛丽安过来看我 好吗?
Please come and see me,and bring Marion,won't you?
我肯定他很快就会来的
I'm sure he'll be here soon.
差不多是时候了 你准备好了吗?
It's almost that time. Are you ready?
准备好了 泰比
I'm ready,Tappy.
别担心 别担心
Not to worry. Not to worry.
你在那儿做什么?
What are you doing there?
你怎么会在这?
Why are you here?
-你想干嘛? -噢 泰比!
-What do you want? -Oh,Tappy!
加入我们 一起创造激情
Join us in creating excellence.
噢 我还以为你不会叫我呢
Oh,I thought you'd never ask.
看这个
Look at this.
-真恶心 -你们想怎么样?
-It's disgusting. -What do you expect?
你们就不能做点好事么?
Could you do any better?
看这个
Look at this.
这是栋老建筑 好几年没粉刷过了
It's an old building. It hasn't been painted in years.
我老了 孤独一人!
I'm old. Alone!
你们不了解
You don't understand.
拜托 我会解释的
Please. I'll explain.
那是什么? 不 我不要!
What is that? No,I don't want that!
你在干什么? 离我远一点!
What are you doing? Get away from me!
-开始了 戈德法布太太 -什么开始了?
-Ready,Mrs Goldfarb. -Ready for what?
三 二...
Three,two...
我要做什么?
What am I supposed to do?
喂我!
Feed me!
你自己去喂他吧
Feed him yourself.
-喂我 莎拉! -喂我 莎拉!
-Feed me,Sara! -Feed me,Sara!
喂我 莎拉!
Feed me,Sara!
喂我 莎拉! 喂我 莎拉!
Feed me,Sara! Feed me,Sara!
我只是想上电视而已 拜托!
I just wanna be on television. Please!
谢啦 安吉尔
Thank you,Angel.
噢... 噢!
Whoo... hoo!
希望这样行得通 我的屁股可以好好热一下了
I sure hope this motherfucker works,man. My ass could use some heat.
-要多久才会到? -一天之内就能到
-How long this trip's gonna take? -I'll make it in a day. No problem.
-一天? -恩
-A day? -yeah.
哈! 加州 我们来了
Shit! California,here we come.
是佛罗里达 泰 佛罗里达
It's Florida,Ty. Florida.
加州 佛罗里达...
California,Florida...
不管哪个 我们都可以去晒晒屁股了
Either way,your pale ass getting a tan.
啊!
Ah!
这辆车到麦迪逊大街吗?
Does this train go to Madison Avenue?!
你知道梅林娱乐集团吗?
Do you know Maylin and Block?
我有他们的地址 就在麦迪逊大街
I have their address. It's on Madison Avenue.
-我就要上电视了 -你累坏了!
-I'm gonna be on television. -You're whacked!
嘿! 嘿! 你好?
Hey! Hey! Hello?
你知道这辆车到麦迪逊大街吗?
Do you know if this train goes to Madison Avenue?
我就要上电视了
I'm gonna be on television!
我只想知道什么时候
I just have to find out when.
佛罗里达?
Florida?
他什么时候回来?
When is he gonna be back?
几天后? 安吉尔 我该怎么办?
A few days? Angel,what am I supposed to do?
你一定要帮我
Please,you gotta help me.
拜托你 我可以给你钱
Oh,come on,I can get you money.
安吉尔 无论如何 一定 要帮我
Angel,there's gotta be something. Anything. Help me.
你们为什么不给我打电话?
Why aren't you calling me?
我要知道我什么时候上电视
I have to know when I'm gonna be on television.
我是莎拉·戈德法布
I'm Sara Goldfarb.
你应该告诉我什么时候上电视
And you should tell me when I'm gonna be on television.
请稍坐一会 我这就通知他们
Just sit for a moment. I'll ring them.
我只是想知道什么时候
I just want to know when.
也许你们弄丢了我的资料 拜托 再查一下 告诉我什么时候
Maybe you lost my card. Please,dolly,you have a look,and you'll tell me.
不是为了得奖 我会把奖励给别人的
It's not the prizes. I'll give them away.
我只是想上节目
I just wanna be on the show.
我等了好久...
I've waited so long...
我想和我的儿子还有我的小孙子在一起
to be on with my Harry and my grandson.
来 戈德法布太太 慢慢喝
Here,Mrs Goldfarb,sip this.
有时候要好一阵子才能通知你上节目
Sometimes it takes a while to get called for a show,Mrs Goldfarb.
哦 哦
Oh. Oooh.
-是她吗? -是
-Is this her? -Yes.
-你能走吗? -我可以在台上走!
-Can you walk? -I'm walkin' across the stage!
你一定要看看我家哈瑞上电视
And you should see my Harry on television.
我们会把奖励给别人
We're giving the prizes away.
我只是想上节目!
I just wanted to be on the show!
-她叫什么名字? -应该是莎拉·戈德法布
-What's her name? -We think it's Sara Goldfarb.
跟西蒙说到美容院接我
Call Seymour and tell him to pick me up at the beauty parlor.
我穿了参加哈瑞毕业典礼的那件红礼服 还有金色的鞋
I've got the red dress that I wore to Harry's graduation,and golden shoes.
好了 戈德法布太太 我们走吧
OK,Mrs Goldfarb. Here we go.
一 二 三...
One, two, three...
放轻松 慢慢来
Let's take it nice and easy.
喂?
Yeah?
嗨...
Hi...
告诉罗丝说我要上电视了
Tell Rose I'm going to be on television.
噢!
Whoo.
噢 靠!
Oh,shit!
天! 你胳膊那样多久了?
God damn Jim! How long you had that?
-只有几天 -看起来不太好
-Just a few days. -That shit don't look too good.
我也觉得很不舒服 老兄
It don't feel too good either,man.
不过来点海洛因就会没事了
But a little stuff will take care of that.
嘿 你有毛病啊 不要打在那里了
Hey,hey! Something's wrong with you. Don't shoot in there!
不这样的话 血管会爆开
I'll blow it if I don't.
妈的
Fuck it.
噢...
Oh...
靠
Shit.
-嗨 还好吗? 能听到我吗? -恩 西蒙
-Hi,how are you? Can you hear me? -Yes,Seymour.
-吃了什么吗? -我穿了红礼服还有...
-Take anything? -I took my red dress and...
-非紧急状况 送她到精神科 -上电视
-No emergency. Take her to psych. -Television.
进来吧
Come on in.
谢谢
Thanks.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
玛丽安
Marion.
呃 你知道吗?
Well,what you know?
罗宾汉里的少女玛丽安
Maid Marion.
我是罗宾汉的助手小约翰
I'm little John.
这里景色不错
You have a Beautiful view...
你知道我最喜欢小女生什么吗?
You know what I like best about paddy chicks?
她们口技都不错
They give good head.
黑妞们就是不会口交
Black broads know nothin' about head.
我也不知道为什么
I don't know why.
也许是风俗习惯的问题吧
Might be it has something to do with some ancient tribal custom.
来吧
Come here.
嗯 最好留点体力
Mmm. Better save some of that energy.
噢 我知道它很漂亮 宝贝
Oh,I know it's pretty,baby,
但它可不是光出来透风的
But I didn't take it out for air.
爽
Yeah.
我跟你说了 笨蛋 不要打在那只胳膊上 疼了吧?
I told your ass,stay away from that arm. See?
我要给玛丽安打电话 老兄
I gotta call Marion,man.
现在可是长途电话喽
That's about to be a long-distance call now.
600英里 我们离迈阿密更近了
That's 600 miles. We are 600 miles closer to Miami.
那我们离纽约更远了
It's also 600 miles further away from New York,Ty.
我知道哪里能弄到高档货
You know I know where to get a real nice taste,
虽然那更像是比赛 星期天晚上...
though it's more like play. Sunday night...
我们有个聚会 都是好人
we're throwing a little gathering. All good people.
不 算了 我很忙
No,I can't,I'm busy.
而且 我的毒瘾也不是很重
Anyway,I'm not really hooked.
哦 但是那高档货可真是不错
Oh,I know,but it's a real nice taste.
星期天见 少女玛丽安
I'll see you Sunday,Maid Marion.
戈德法布太太 试着回答我的问题 好吗?
OK,Mrs Goldfarb. Just try and answer my questions,OK?
-你从什么时候开始服用药片的? -哦 夏天
-When did you start taking pills? -Oh,summer.
-你从去年夏天开始服用? -我在晒太阳
-So you started last summer? -I got the best place in the sun.
-艾达在帮我整理头发 -都会好起来的 戈德法布太太
-Ada fixed my hair. -Everything is gonna be all right,Mrs Goldfarb.
我们很快就会治好你的
We'll get you fixed up in no time.
-撑着点 老兄 -我真的撑不下去了
-Hold tight,man. Hold tight. -I can't cut it. I can't fucking cut it.
得想点办法 泰
I gotta do something about my arm,Ty.
让我看看怎么样了
Let me see what it looks like.
噢 天啊 靠!
Oh, damn, Jim!
噢 老兄
Oh, man.
没见过比这再恶心的了
That's the ugliest motherfucker I've ever seen.
-我要给玛丽安打电话 -他妈的
-I gotta call Marion. -Fuck that.
我要把你送进医院 老兄
We gotta get you to a hospital,man.
那是什么?
What is that?
我不要 我不要!
I don't want that. I don't want that!
啊 呃...
Ah, Oh...
怎么了?
What's the problem?
-我的胳膊 我的胳膊痛得要命 -我来看一下
-It's my arm. My arm is killin' me. -Let's have a look at it.
好吧
All right.
我等一下就回来
I'll be back in a minute.
我想通宵玩二十一点
I wanna just play blackjack all night long.
所以我就来排班 我说 "你们去吧 我不是很舒服"
So I make up this routine. I told "you gays go ahead. I don't feel good.You gays go..."
然后他们就离开了
Sure enough,they leave the room..
好了吗? 一 二 三
Ready? One,two and three.
他们一离开
As soon as they leave,
我就跑回赌场继续玩二十一点
I go running back to the casino,sit at my blackjack table.
我整晚都泡在那里
I am there for the whole night.
最后 我赢了不少 我口袋里有五个一百的筹码
Finally,I get up so big,I got five $100 black chips in my pocket.
我发誓 过了一会
I swear to God. The hours are going by.
我又跟一个十七岁的辣妹搭讪 真是爽呆了
I'm laying back,hitting on a hard 17s. It was beautiful.
然后呢
Next thing I know,
一位保安坐在我旁边 叫我离开
This gay sitting next to me is the security guard and telling me I have to leave.
我说 "你为什么要我离开?"
I asked why,"Why you telling me I have to leave?"
他说 "因为你..."
He said,"You have to leave because..."
吞下
Swallow.
吞下去
你要吃东西 如果你想痊愈的话就要吃东西
You have to eat,Mrs Goldfarb. If we're gonna get you healthy you have to eat.
配合护理人员的工作 好吗? 我会试一些新的药看看
Ok? Trying to Work with the attendants. I'm gonna try some new medications.
-你好? -玛丽安
-Hello? -Marion.
哈瑞
Harry.
玛丽安 我好想你
Marion,I've been thinking about you so much.
你还好吗?
Are you OK?
-你什么时候回家? -快了
-When you comin' home? - Soon.
什么时候?
When?
就快了
Soon.
-你再坚持一下好吗? -哈瑞?
-You holdin' out all right? -Harry?
你今天能回来吗?
Can you come today?
恩
Yeah.
我会回去
I'll come.
我今天会回去
I'll come today.
等着我 好吗?
You just wait for me,all right?
-好 哈瑞 -我就回去了 玛丽安
-OK,Harry. -I'm coming back,Marion.
-恩 -玛丽安?
-Yeah. -Marion?
嗯?
Yeah?
我真的很抱歉 玛丽安
I'm really sorry,Marion.
我知道
I know.
戈德法布太太?
Mrs Goldfarb?
你还好吗?
You all right?
呃 是这样的 我们已经试了多种药物治疗
Um,so,Mrs Goldfarb,we've tried several medications,
不过好像都没什么效果
And you don't seem to be responding.
我相信我们该换种治疗方法了
I believe we might come to a point where we might try some alternative methods.
我们的电休克疗法效果一直不错
We've had excellent results with ECT in the past.
呃... 如果你可以
Um... So if I can just...
在这里签下名...
Get your John Hancock...
我们就可以进行了
We'll get underway.
很好 谢谢
Great. Thanks.
噢 天啊!
Oh,Jesus Christ!
我需要医生 老兄
I need a doctor,man.
我朋友病了 谁能帮他一下 拜托
My friend is sick. Give him some help,please.
我受不了了 老兄 我的胳膊! 他妈的我的胳膊!
I can't take it,man. My arm! My fuckin' arm!
救我!
Help me!
来个人帮帮我们 拜托!
Help us. Somebody fuckin' help us,please!
少女玛丽安 欢迎
Maid Marion. Welcome.
听得到? 看得到?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
-是的 长官 -可以工作
-Yes,sir. -OK for work.
听得到? 看得到?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
-是的 长官 -可以工作
-Yes,sir. -OK for work.
听得到? 看得到?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
-是的 长官 -可以工作
-Yes,sir. -OK for work.
听得到? 看得到?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
-是的 长官 -可以工作
-Yes,sir. -OK for work.
听得到? 看得到?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
-是的 长官 -可以工作
-Yes,sir. -OK for work.
伙计们 这就是玛丽安
Fellas,meet Marion.
听得到? 看得到?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
-是的 长官 -可以工作
-Yes,sir. -OK for work.
听得到? 看得到?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
-是的 长官 -可以工作
-Yes,sir. -OK for work.
好戏上场了
Show time.
可以工作 听得到? 看得到?
OK for work. Can you hear me? Can you see me?
是
Yes.
说长官 妈的纽约毒鬼
Say "sir". Goddam New York dope fiend niggers.
学点礼貌
Learn some manners.
听得到? 看得到?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
-是的 长官 -可以工作
-Yes,sir. -OK for work.
-戴上护齿套 -听得到? 看得到?
-Got a mouthpiece. -Can you hear me? Can you see me?
听说他的胳膊有点问题
Says he's got something wrong with his arm.
我想他没法再在那里注射毒品了
I don't think he'll put any more dope in that arm.
-闻起来比他还糟 -测试
-Smells worse than he do. -Test.
还是把他送到医院吧 别死在这了
Better get him over to the hospital. I don't expect he'll live out the week.
好了吗? 来... 一
Ready? And... one.
你们这些毒虫都是这样
That's the trouble with you dope fiends.
你们态度很差 你知道吗?
You got a rotten attitude. You know that,man?
-现在我们要做什么? -屁眼对屁眼
-So what are we gonna do now? -Ass to ass.
屁眼对屁眼!
Ass to ass!
把你们那玩意放进自己的屁眼里 快点!
Put your spineless back into it. Come on!
好了吗? 来... 二!
Ready? And... two!
屁眼对屁眼!
Ass to ass!
-放进去 -就是这样
-Put it in there. -That's it.
放轻松 慢慢来
Nice and easy.
土豆泥!
Mashed potatoes!
马上到 我需要1克 对
Here's the close. I need one gram. Bingo.
别停下 别停下 动起来 动起来!
Don't give up. Don't give up. Move it,move it,move it!
好
OK.
好了吗? 来.. 三
Ready? And... three!
射吧 射吧 射吧 射吧
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
肩膀以下都要切除
We're gonna take it off at the shoulder.
射吧 射吧 射吧 射吧
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
锯子
Saw.
玛丽安!
Marion!
没事了 别担心 你在医院里
It's all right. Don't worry. You're in a hospital.
-玛丽安? -谁?
-Marion? -Who's that?
我们会通知她的 她会来的
She'll be sent for. She'll come.
-不 -不?
-No. -No?
不 她不会来了
No,she won't.
她会来的
She'll come.
优胜者出来了! 优胜者出来了!
All right! We got a winner. We got a winner.
优胜者来了! 优胜者出来了!
We got a winner! We got a winner!
我们的下位优胜者人见人爱
Our next winner is that delightful personality,
她来自布鲁克林
straight from Brighton Beach,Brooklyn.
让我们热烈欢迎 莎拉·戈德法布太太
Please,give a juicy welcome to Mrs Sara Goldfarb!
很高兴告诉你 你获得了特等奖
I'm delighted to tell you that you have just won the grand prize!
-噢 不会吧 -让我告诉你 大奖是什么
-Oh,no. -Let me tell you what you've won.
你的大奖有着迷人的笑容 他有自己的事业
Your prize has a sweet smile and his own private business.
他刚订婚 而且将在今年夏天完成终身大事
He just got engaged, and is about to get married this summer.
让我们热情地欢迎 哈瑞·戈德法布!
Please give a warm and juicy welcome, Harry Goldfarb!
哈瑞热情有劲! 哈瑞热情有劲!
Juice by Harry! Juice by Harry! Juice by Harry!
噢! 哈瑞真来劲! 哈瑞真来劲!
Ohh! Harry juice! Harry juice!
噢 哈瑞!
Ohh, Harry!
-我爱你 哈瑞 -我也爱你 妈
-I love you, Harry. -I love you too, Ma.